investorsalley.com 2013-06-09

# Investors Alley: Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

  |  **PRIVACY STATEMENT | TERMS OF USE/DISCLAIMER | COPYRIGHT**

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Investors Alley Corp. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. In order to provide service to our customers, we must obtain some limited personal information from you. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website and service.

### Summary

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our website and the web. We use aggregated (gathered up data across all user accounts) information to develop content targeted to users' interests and to better the website user experience. Investors Alley is committed to your privacy and other than as provided herein or after receiving your specific consent, we will not share any personal information with any third party at any time, unless required by law. 

When you visit InvestorsAlley.com or inquire about our services, we may collect the following types of information about you: 

At certain times, it may be necessary to share the information you provide. InvestorsAlley.com does not share your personally identifiable information with third parties unless it is related to fulfilling the services you've asked us to perform, or as is permitted by law. The information you provide us can only be shared under limited circumstances. These include: 

### Our Security Safeguards

We employ industry-standard physical, electronic, and procedural security safeguards to protect the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. Whenever we prompt you to transmit sensitive information, such as a credit card number, to us through our website, we support encryption of your data as it is transmitted. 

### Public Forums

InvestorsAlley.com makes chat rooms, forums, and message boards available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Correcting/Opting Out

InvestorsAlley.com offers its members the ability to correct or update the information we collected during registration online by utilizing the appropriate links at the bottom of all emails we send out. 

If, at any time, you wish to cancel your subscription to our service or opt-out of receiving future mailings or certain types of mailings, please click the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of all emails we send out. You may also [use this website](http://www.investorsalley.com/info/emails.html) for removal. 

### Advertiser Information

Investors Alley derives the majority of its revenue from advertising and sharing information is essential to keeping our services affordable to users. In order to attract and retain advertisers we use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather (as well as information from third-party market researchers) to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our audience. We do not disclose personally identifying information about our users to these parties.

These offers are paid advertisements provided by our external partners or external advertisers. If you click on these offers, you will be proceeding under the terms of that third party advertiser's privacy policy. Investors Alley is not responsible for the content of thes advertisements. Investors Alley makes no guarantee nor warranty about what is advertised. 

These advertisements may contain information about specific stocks, but the opinions in these advertisements are not those of Investors Alley and are neither an offer nor a recommendation to buy or sell any security. We have not independently verified the validify of the claims or statements contained in these advertisements/emails. We urge you to always conduct your own research and due diligence and obtain professional advice before making any investment decision. We will not be liable for any loss or damage caused by a reader's reliance on information obtained in advertisements or corresponding web sites.

Although Investors Alley attempts to accept advertisements from responsible third party advertisers, we make no representations or guarantees about such third parties. You understand that if you choose to register with or enter into a transaction with any third-party advertiser based on an advertisement or offer found on an Investors Alley web site, within an Investors alley email, or via any other delivery method (including, but not limited to, postal mail) that such a third party advertiser is separate from Investors Alley and that Investors Alley is not responsible or liable for any action or omission by the third-party advertiser.

We respect the privacy of our users and shall not disclose or distribute our user list to any third party, nor shall we permit anyone else to do so. However, we do make available for rental our list of registrants to advertising clients. However, these advertisers never see your actual email address. They may be able to use tracking software to reveal your email address if you choose to click a link in the email message.

### Co-Registration

We only transmit your information to a third-party advertiser if you elect to receive a special offer from that advertiser through our co-registration service (either by selecting or by leaving selected the check box next to the advertiser's offer). The information we transmit in this instance may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address, phone number, IP address and the date you registered for the third party offer. We may also transmit information about our visitors and subscribers collected through the registration process as well as through any online surveys we may conduct. 

### Links

Our website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. We strongly encourage you to be aware when you leave our site or click a link in our emails and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by us.

### Former Customers

We treat information concerning our former customers the same way we treat information about our current customers. InvestorsAlley.com discloses personal information about former customers only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Contacting Us

Questions or comments regarding this policy should be directed to: 

Investors Alley Corp.   
245 Park Avenue   
39th Floor   
New York, NY 10167   
Phone: (212) 566-6100 

We reserve the right to modify this policy without notice.

**TERMS OF USE/DISCLAIMER**

Use of this site is covered under the following disclaimer, terms, and conditions. As a condition to accessing Investors Alley materials, emails, and websites, you the site visitor or email subscriber, agree to the following. 

Investors Alley Corp. is a publisher of financial news and opinions and is NOT a securities broker/dealer or an investment advisor. You are responsible for your own investment decisions. All information contained in our emails or on our website(s) should be independently verified with the companies mentioned, and readers should always conduct their own research and due diligence and consider obtaining professional advice before making any investment decision. 

Investors Alley Corp. furnishes information without responsibility for accuracy and it is accepted by the site visitor/email subscriber on the condition that error in transmission or omissions shall not be made the basis for any claim, demand or cause for action against Investors Alley Corp. or any of its information providers, including independent contributors. Investors Alley Corp. relies on various sources of information that it believes to be accurate and reliable. However, Investors Alley Corp. makes no claims or representations with regard to the accuracy, completeness, or truth of any material contained herein. All information provided on Investors Alley.com is to be used on an "as is, with all faults" basis. 

You agree that you bear responsibility for your own investment research and investment decisions, and that Investors Alley Corp. or its independent contributors shall not be liable for any decision made or action taken by you or others based upon reliance on news, information, or any material published by Investors Alley Corp. 

Investors Alley Corp. and its independent contributors do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness or timeliness of, or otherwise endorse, these views, opinions or recommendations, give investment advice, or advocate the purchase or sale of any security or investment. 

**COPYRIGHT INFORMATION**

All information contained within this site is the property of Investors Alley Corp. and is protected under copyright. None of the material may be reproduced, including posting to news groups and message boards, without the prior written consent of Investors Alley Corp., with the exception of downloading or printing a single copy for yourself for offline viewing. However, you may provide a hypertext link to the Investors Alley.com site or any article/page within the site. 

Investors Alley Corp. reserves the right to republish the material contributed by its readers. By sending an e-mail with feedback, comments, suggestions, or criticism (including from the feedback page, you expressly grant the right to Investors Alley Corp. to republish or sell the comments/message as part of its edited compilations. The company will provide proper attribution to the author for any post or e-mail it republishes. 

* * *

© [Copyright](http://www.investorsalley.com/info/copyright.html) 1998-2013, Investors Alley Corp. All rights reserved.     [Contact Us](http://www.investorsalley.com/info/contact.html)

|   |
